[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 28]
I'm fine.
But I've already told Liu Shao
that
I'm going back to the Immortal Palace with her.
What did you say?
Didn't you say you'd stay a few more days?
But I don't want to anymore.
Did Liu Shao tell you something?
No.
I thought it through.
Maybe
an immortal and a demon
really shouldn't be together.
The old Demon King and Fairy Ze Shui
are our best lesson.
Now that
you have regained your freedom,
stay in the Palace of Aquatic Demons
and be the General of Water.
I'm going back to the Immortal Palace
and be Fairy Luo Ning.
From now on,
we'll go our separate ways
and never meet again.
Isn't that better?
No.
I disagree.
Whatever.
Anyway,
I won't come to the Palace of Aquatic Demons again.
Don't come to the Immortal Palace either.
I said
I disagree.
What do you want then?
You want to learn from the Demon King
and imprison me for life
or just kill me?
No.
I'm sorry.
In one night,
Luo Ning was totally different.
It must be Liu Shao.
Why is she leaving all of a sudden?
Luo Ning said she really missed her brother,
so she wanted to go back as soon as possible.
You're worried about Luo Ge too, and want to go back,
right?
In order to be with him,
you can bear any pain.
You can even seal the divine spirit.
You only think of my brother
when you need him.
At other times,
no matter how much he does,
you can't see it, right?
Fu.
What?
Did I say anything wrong?
Do you dare to show her the wound on your right arm?
After all this time,
she still doesn't know that your right arm has been broken.
He Na.
When pacifying demons,
it's inevitable to get hurt when encountering some powerful opponents.
I've already recovered long ago.
No wonder
you've been holding the flute with your left hand.
I was careless.
I'm sorry.
Shouldn't you ask him
how he got injured?
With the power of the Demon King in White,
he can even fight Immortal Feelingless.
Which demon is so powerful as to hurt him?
Enough, Fu.
Why?
When you saved her in the furnace,
has she ever thought about
what it's like for an aquatic demon
to be roasted by fire?
If you were not badly injured inside,
how could a mountain demon
break your arm?
It was an accident.
It's not your fault.
Fu.
What's wrong with you today?
Liu Shao.
Let me ask you.
What did you tell Luo Ning?
Why did she suddenly want to leave
and cut ties with me?
I want to know.
What did you say to her?
Or is it something you did?
I didn't.
And Luo Ning
is the treasure of Luo Ge
and the Immortal Palace.
She is also the heir of Immortal Ze Shui.
Who else can I get back at other than her?
She threw herself at me. She was stupid.
Do you want me to be like you,
someone who can't even keep the woman delivered to your door?
Fu.
The Three-legged Golden Crow and the Crown Wheel are the doppelgangers of the God of the Sun.
They all share the power of the God of the Sun's divine spirit.
I found these too.
He forced us
to read ancient books all night and think of solutions.
But he himself meditated comfortably.
He's an animal.
It seems Master Shang is not afraid of the sealing spell.
Right?
You...
Shut up!
You didn't even check the book closely.
You're just waiting for Liu Shao and Ning
to return to the Immortal Palace to help you, right?
Demon King asked me to come alone.
Do you have something to tell me?
Fairy Luo Ning.
Fu is impetuous.
Sometimes he talks without thinking
and doesn't care about others'feelings.
If he offended you,
please forgive him.
You called me
just to tell me this?
Fairy Luo Ning,
sometimes
Fu talks before he thinks,
but it's not what he really means.
Well said.
To see the nature of a person,
you should not just
observe his deeds.
His words
are important too.
Luo Ning.
This is for you.
This
is the same as the one my brother gave to Liu Shao.
I made this out of my demon energy.
You can use it to summon me.
No.
I also put a thread of my spirit into it.
If
I did something wrong to you,
stick needles in it.
It will definitely hurt me.
If you still feel angry,
you can just crush it.
I won't be able to get up.
Really?
Fu.
Demon King.
Goodbye.
Fu.
What are you doing?
She must've heard
what I said before.
If I don't do this,
she won't be able to vent her anger.
Since you like her,
you should be careful with your words and actions.
Don't you feel sad
when you made her angry?
But look.
She doesn't want me to hurt.
She put my pearl away.
After I left the Immortal Palace,
it's not easy for me to inquire about the Immortal Palace.
If she brings my spirit in,
it's like giving me a chance
to go in and out of the Immortal Palace freely.
Luo Ge is back.
The demon world is unified.
The three worlds are about to live in harmony.
Why do you have to do this?
No matter how harmonious the three worlds are,
we're still living by water.
Are you really afraid of the Immortal Palace
and just want to be a coward?
You...
I'm fine.
Go back.
Okay.
The God of the Sun's Crown Wheel can stop all evil spirits.
That's right. There are many things that the Crown Wheel can do.
I heard that
the Crown Wheel was made by
the God of the Sun with the broken pieces of her divine spirit
and the magic water of the Three-legged Golden Crow.
I heard that...
Liu Shao is back.
Yo.
You're back.
Liu Shao is back.
She didn't come to Palace Chonghua first.
Luo Ge.
You can't beat
Demon King in White who is gentle and considerate.
Is the Tears of the Half-Demon really so useful?
It's useless to me here anyway.
Take it.
Thank you, Luo Ning.
Have you really made up your mind?
Sealing the spirit is no joke.
But...
It's better than us not being together
and hurting each other without knowing it.
Then you'd better seal it.
Remember.
Don't tell your brother
about this.
That's easy for you to say.
How can I hide this?
Look.
We have to pick a date and set up a formation.
We have to ask the masters for help.
Besides,
my brother will find out sooner or later.
Knowing afterwards
and watching me suffer
are two different things.
All right.
As you know,
your brother seems cold
and doesn't talk much,
but he values love and loyalty.
I'm afraid once he knows,
he will blame himself
and suffer every day
before I sealed it.
If he loses his cultivation...
Liu Shao.
My brother is lucky
to have met you.
It's not easy for people who love each other
to be together.
I know
I should cherish my blessings.
You suddenly asked us to read ancient books,
do you want to find a fast way
to ascend to an immortal?
Get everything ready.
I'm doing this to help Liu Shao
cultivate her spiritual power.
You pretended to be so heartless.
Why would you cry with my water energy?
We'll go our separate ways
and never meet again.
You wish!
I won't let you escape.
Give me some more time.
For you,
for my clan,
I have my duties.
You promised to save my junior.
What are you waiting for?
What's the rush?
Leave it to me.
Come out, Fu.
I've suppressed Xie Lingqi.
What is so important that
I have to take such a big risk to get it myself?
A relic of the God of the Moonlight.
I purified and refined it
with my only remaining power of the God of the Moonlight.
The relic of the God of the Moonlight?
Yes.
Do you know it belongs to Xie Lingqi
and it comes from the Yin-yang Cave?
I see.
And you kept using his stuff
again and again.
Luo Ge will find out sooner or later.
Of course I know.
Do you think I'm afraid of him?
You're crazy.
Bone Melting Pool.
Immortal Luo Ge?
Aren't you looking for me?
What?
Are you surprised?
What are you trying to do
by deliberately revealing where you are?
Am I not you?
You don't even know what I want to do?
Your ability to escape is comparable to that of the General,
but don't teach fish to swim in front of me.
I happen to be sick of this body.
How useless.
You can't even protect the medicine.
It's a waste of my time.
Tell me.
Do you know who did it?
I think it was a woman.
A woman?
I smelled the fragrance of flowers.
The thing that took this bottle was cold.
It looks like a drop of water.
Could it be
Luo Ning?
That means
the evil spirit leaked out.
It's hidden
in Xie Lingqi's body.
I've removed the evil spirit in Xie Lingqi's body.
But I suspect there are other evil spirits
in the Immortal Palace.
Speaking of hidden evil spirits,
it must be the Yin-yang Cave
in the Immortal Palace.
Yin-yang Cave?
That place
used to be the place where my father was sealed.
There are a lot of insignificant evil spirits inside.
Since they were sealed by the Protection Spell,
there's nothing to worry about.
But
if the evil spirits in the cave are too turbulent,
they will leak out of the Four Seasons Monument.
Back then,
I was hurt by the evil spirit.
I grasped the Burning Sea 500 years ago.
So what?
That evil spirit
has damaged my immortal root.
If I don't remove it with Xilun Formation,
I will never become an Immortal.
But as you know,
how much it takes
to open the Xilun Formation?
The price is too high.
I can't afford it.
If you had told Zhuo Qiuxian
about this earlier,
I believe
she wouldn't have forced you to cultivate into an Immortal.
But it was my senior's wish for thousands of years
that I cultivate into an Immortal.
If she had to use the Xilun Formation
and sacrifice herself,
by then,
what should I do?
So
you'd rather listen to her nagging and get beaten by her
than tell her?
What can I do?
She is my senior.
Shang Yurong.
Get lost!
That heartless Luo Ge.
Master Shang.
What did Immortal Luo Ge do?
You said he has no conscience again.
It's none of your business.
Look at you, cursing like a shrew.
No wonder Master Zhuo looks so angry.
Don't talk about my senior.
Where is she?
Senior.
It's my fault.
I should have been cultivating in the Palace of Abyssal Mirrors.
Luo Ge insisted that
I tell him something about the past.
Senior.
What did I do wrong?
Haven't you grasped the Burning Sea long ago?
Why didn't you use it?
Are you dumb?
Aren't you
usually quite talkative?
Zhuo Qiuxian.
Enough!
This is between Shang Yurong and me.
It's none of your business.
Do you really want to kill him?
Come in and talk.
I made a pot of good tea.
If he wants to cultivate into an Immortal,
he must sacrifice
a General or above.
He can't ascend to an Immortal.
He was also afraid that you would sacrifice for him.
He would rather lie to you forever
and make you resent him
for not going forward.
For the past 1,000 years,
he has been carrying this secret alone.
Even though he is said to be
the most undeserving master of the three palaces,
he just didn't want to sacrifice anyone,
and
he didn't want you to be sad for him.
You knew I would come,
and prepared such a big gift for me.
If I didn't prepare this gift for you,
I wouldn't know
how long you will take me for a fool.
I didn't take you for a fool.
I...
I did hide some things from you.
For example, I saved Bai Feng.
But that's not because I wanted to do it.
It's because she used me before.
And I also saw that she's useful to me.
That's why I saved her.
It's not what you think.
Really?
Bai Feng assassinated the Immortal Master
and almost killed my brother and Liu Shao.
When you saved her,
have you ever thought about me?
That was in the past.
But can you also think about
how good I was to you?
You're shameless!
Luo Ning!
Luo Ning,
don't be mad at me.
If you want to vent your anger,
can you hit me?
Can you scold me?
Stop being hypocritical.
You've been lying to me
from the beginning.
Even...
Even that night.
So,
do you even despise and shun me,
a monster who lives on water
and will die out of it?
You keep showing your weakness
to seek my sympathy.
♫The begonia is red, but every promise makes it more withered♫
After I revealed your true identity,
it's still the same.
Originally,
♫It blooms alone, but the wind and rain are more violent♫
I didn't want to unmask you.
But what I got in the end
♫Plants are not human beings, and ruthless fruits are planted♫
is your
water energy pearl full of wicked thoughts.
♫How can you forget the innocence and ignorance when we first met?♫
Tell me.
How many times have you
entered the Immortal Palace with this pearl?
I admit
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
I did come here.
But I just came to see you.
I didn't do anything.
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
Fu.
You've been lying to me from the beginning.
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of fire, they lost each other♫
How can I trust you again?
Or do you
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
think I am stupid?
Take your water energy pearl.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
Leave now.
From now on,
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
don't ever come here again.
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
Luo Ning.
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
I beg you.
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
No matter how many mistakes I made,
my love for you has never been fake.
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
I won't give up us.
Nor do I allow you to give up on us.
Please.
Keep this
and let me visit you at the Immortal Palace, okay?
I just want to see you.
Stop dreaming.
Leave now.
Otherwise,
I'll open the Protection Spell in this room
and let someone throw you into the Bone Melting Pool.
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
You wouldn't do that.
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
Indeed.
I wouldn't.
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of fire, they lost each other♫
You're sure that
my feelings for you are real.
From the beginning,
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
all my feelings for you
was part of your plan,
right?
No.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
Because
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
I hold you in my palm.
I value you more than my life.
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
You wouldn't be so cruel.
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
Fu.
♫I'm willing to spread my wings♫
You're right.
♫And don't fight the fate♫
I really don't want to hurt you.
♫It's a good moment to share the world with you♫
But I don't want to
see you again for the rest of my life.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
Fu.
Who hurt your spirit like this?
Is it Fairy Luo Ning?
Mr. Tai.
I'm going to overthrow the world.
I'm going to trap Luo Ning
in the Palace of Aquatic Demons
so that she can never
leave me.
Fu.
But you're no match for Immortal Luo Ge
or His Majesty.
If I...
If I get the demon energy of the Demon King...
The demon energy left by the Demon King
held up the world of Aquatic Demons.
If you get it,
your ability can surpass the Demon King.
But the Aquatic Demons
will...
Do you really think
my brother and I are no match for
the Immortal Palace?
That's just because my brother is kind and refused.
Fu.
Do you mean that
if he refuses...
I'll force him to do it.
Why is she already asleep at this hour?
Fairy has been quite sleepy lately.
Should I wake her up?
No need.
She's been too quiet lately.
I'm worried about her.
Take good care of her
and let her rest.
Also,
I secretly hid some of the homework
her brother gave her.
As for the rest,
let her recite if she can.
If she can't, she can pretend to be sick.
Yes.
You like me so much.
You should be willing to
recite all my homework for this month, right?
[Meditation Spell]
Meditation Spell?
♫This is a spring song♫
What?
You don't want to?
I will do it.
Of course I'll recite for you.
♫The peach blossoms fly with the swallow♫
♫Whose lights are light and shine people's way home?♫
How about I be your brother?
And
♫The clouds roll the sunset♫
♫The moon kisses the eyebrows♫
I want to protect you too.
♫I am waiting for you to say♫
Let you be a happy little fairy.
♫Tonight in this life♫
Luo Ning.
I really appreciate it that
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
I met you in the Immortal Palace.
♫I miss you so much♫
Don't ever come here again.
♫I still remember the youth♫
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning, I beg you.
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
No matter how many mistakes I made,
my love for you has never been fake.
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
I value you more than my life.
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
You wouldn't be so cruel.
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
♫Send you to the Western State♫
What are true?
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
What are fake?
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
Fu.
How many times have you lied to me?
Can I still trust you?
Did I give my heart
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
to the wrong person?
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
♫Send you to the Western State♫
I'm asked to lead the demons to riot.
Will the Aquatic Demons listen to me?
I'll deal with the Palace of Aquatic Demons.
You just need to throw the mortal world into chaos
and wait for my instructions.
Throw the mortal world into chaos?
Is it a safe plan?
I'm afraid the Demon King...
That's different.
I'm not the only one behind you.
There is also the one
who can check and balance Luo Ge.
Cleansing the heart.
Luo Ge.
Do you feel disconcerted?
I am you.
How can you get rid of me?
Even if you can cleanse this small area,
I am
not only here.
Luo Ge.
I'm everywhere in the three worlds.
Go and take a look at
what the people you protect are chasing.
Hypocrisy.
Love and lust.
Obsession.
Greed.
Deception.
Selfishness.
Fight.
Power.
Envy.
Unwillingness.
Prejudice.
Arrogance.
I'm everywhere.
I'm coming.
Be careful.
Who is it?
Who is destroying Aquatic Demons?
[Mansion of Wu Yang Duke]
Hurry.
Hurry!
Ask for help from the Immortal Palace.
No, no.
You can't go.
You really can't go.
Immortal wants you to cultivate in peace.
Do you want me to watch the innocent die?
Immortal Master Wanwu said
he would send the disciples of the Immortal Palace to rescue them.
I'm familiar with the Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
I can help those disciples.
Let me go.
Help!
The ground is cracking.
Hold on.
Stand firm.
If we're thrown on the water,
we'll all be dead.
His Majesty will save us.
Hold on.
My brother is stabilizing the demon world.
I'll take a look.
Your Majesty,
it was you
who stabilized the demon world by yourself.
Where's Fu?
[Elegant and Graceful]
It's a fairy.
A fairy is here to save us.
[Mansion of Wu Yang Duke]
Liu Shao.
I knew you would come to help us.
Wang Jian, Xue,
are you okay?
We're fine.
It's just that the demons are coming in a fierce manner
and hurting civilians everywhere.
Now,
we are also in fear.
We don't know what to do.
Didn't Immortal Master
send the disciples of the Immortal Palace to help?
Something must have delayed them on the way.
No one else has been here.
What about He Na?
He is the Demon King.
He won't sit by.
We sent someone to the Moon Washing Pond to inform them.
But something happened to the Aquatic Demons too.
No one responded.
Bad things happen in the mortal world and the demon world at the same time.
What are the chances?
Don't worry about
Mansion of Wu Yang Duke.
I've sent disciples to the mortal world to check.
As for the crisis in the demon world,
the Aquatic Demons
always solve their own problems.
Focus on your cultivation.
Don't be disturbed by these problems.
I'll check the Four Seasons Monument later.
You stay here
and continue your cultivation.
It doesn't matter.
I'll go with you.
Liu Shao.
I have a bad feeling.
There seems to be some power surging.
I wonder if anything happened
with He Na.
I've used up all my demon power
to protect the underwater demon world.
Looks like we have to find another way.
Do you admit your mistake?
What did I do wrong?
You stole the demon king's demon energy
and almost destroyed our foundation of ten thousand years.
Foundation of ten thousand years?
Brother.
I really forgot
our foundation is on land.
All the demons had to listen to us.
If we don't break the Four Seasons Monument
and beg the Supreme God to break the curse on our clan,
we will not have the chance to return to land.
Brother, you don't know, do you?
I heard that there's an auspicious sign in the sky.
Luo Ge is about to be deified.
When will you
face the reality?
I asked our clansmen if they would
live like cowards or die fighting.
Listen to our generals' answer.
We are willing to fight to the death.
We don't want to live like cowards.
We will smash the Immortal Palace
and return to land.
Mr. Tai.
Do you think so too?
Your Majesty, please go to the Immortal Palace,
break the Four Seasons Monument,
release the God of the Moonlight,
and lift the curse on our clan!
Release the God of the Moonlight,
Do you know
the one under the Four Seasons Monument
has long been contaminated by evil spirits.
He's no longer a pure God of the Moonlight.
Once he is out in the world,
the three worlds will be in chaos
and all living things will be in misery.
When I was in the Immortal Palace,
the Supreme God once appeared in my dream.
He promised to break the curse
after he's released.
What does the rest
have to do with us?
Your Majesty, please go to the Immortal Palace
break the Four Seasons Monument,
release the God of the Moonlight,
and lift the curse on our clan!
Release the God of the Moonlight,